

<u>alirezarastineh95@gmail.com</u>

alirezarastineh



alirezarastineh.me



Berlin, Germany

in <u>alirezarastineh</u>



Profile

Front End Developer with academic expertise in Software Engineering and Digital Media & Computing, ready to excel in a Front End Development role.

Personal Details

Nationality: German - Iranian Date of Birth: 21.01.1995

Tech Skills

5 HTML5



JavaScript



ൽ React.js



B Bootstrap



MongoDB





Firebase



Git



CSS3



TypeScript



Next.js





Tailwind CSS



(s) Node.js



🖄 GraphQL



(REST API



ջ⊠ Jest

Soft Skills

- Problem-Solving
- · Teamwork and Collaboration
- Effective Communication
- Adaptability
- Objection Handling

Language Skills

- German C2 (Proficient)
- English B2 (Upper Intermediate)
- Persian (Native)

Alireza Rastineh

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Experiences

Full Stack Developer

Code Academy Berlin Education GmbH

March - August 2023

- 5-Month Program: 840 Hours of Practical Projects.
- Agile/SCRUM Framework: Consistent application in group projects.
- · Code Reviews: Promoting quality and learning.
- Presentations: Effective communication of project progress.

Professional Sprinter

SCC Berlin & German National Team

December 2013 - March 2023

- Championship Titles 2018: Berlin and Brandenburg champion in 100m and 4x100m.
- German National Team: Competed in the 4x100m relay.
- Link: ATHLETE CODE: 14705514

COO-Assistant & Sales Assistant

Allianz Versicherung Roskos & Meier OHG

February 2020 - February 2023

- Staff Deployment Coordination: Increased efficiency through coordination of internal
- Data Management: Managed customer data using the AMS broker program for financial services.

Educational History

Practice-oriented Sales Training

TENTE-TRAINING

October 2023 - Present

Enrolled in:

B. Sc. Digital Media and Computing (Part-Time)

University of Applied Sciences Berlin

April 2021 - March 2023

Graduated in:

B. Sc. Computer Engineering - Software (N.c.: 1.6)

Azad University Science and Research Branch of Tehran September 2013 - July 2018 (Distance Educational System)

Latest Projects

AlirezaBaba

E-Commerce Plattform

June - July 2023

- Technologies: MERN Stack with TypeScript and Bootstrap (responsive).
- Features: User authentication. Admin dashboard. PayPal payment integration.
- Links: AlirezaBaba & GitHub

Cryptocurrency Club

Cryptocurrency Information Website May - June 2023

- Technologies: JavaScript, React, Tailwind CSS, Firebase and Real-time API (responsive).
- · Features: Real-time statistics. User authorization and authentication. Watchlist.
- Links: Cryptocurrency Club & GitHub